Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can master
all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Korra and Jinora have entered
the spirit world.
With Tenzin's daughter
as her spiritual guide,
the Avatar has one mission:
To close the spirit portal
before harmonic convergence.
Meanwhile, Unalaq
has been working
with the dark spirit Vaatu,
who was imprisoned
by Avatar Wan 10,000 years ago.
Will Korra be able
to close the portal
and stop Unalaq from enacting
his deadly plan?
[Tense string music]
I can't believe my little girl
had to guide Korra
into the spirit world
instead of me.
If anything happens to her,
I won't be able
to forgive myself.
She's very smart,
and she obviously has
a strong connection
to the spirits.
She'll be fine.
Yeah, dad went all the time.
They won't have their bending
in there.
They'll be defenseless.
[Clears throat]
Excuse me,
but I've never had bending,
and I don't think
I'd call myself "defenseless."
Of course you aren't,
because you have your, um...
Positive attitude?
I would have said
acute intellect
and catlike reflexes,
but whatever.
Why don't you two
get some sleep?
I'll take the first watch.
Wake us up if you need
some company.
Or if any interesting
spirity stuff happens,
like their bodies start
floating around
and you need someone
to help you grab them
before they fly off.
Bumi.
I'm just saying we're here
if you need us.
I know you are.
Thank you.
Please come back soon.
Isn't it beautiful?
Just stick close to me, okay?
This seems nice,
but you never know
when we'll run
into some dark spirits.
Huh.
Look.
[Chuckles]
It's like it's made of jewels.
The spirits are
so much more beautiful
in their own world
than they are at home.
Jinora, be careful.
Hold on.
[Shouts] Hey.
Watch where you're goin',
you giant clod.
Sorry.
This is a residential area,
in case you hadn't noticed.
Who do you think you are,
stomping through here
like that?
I'm the Avatar.
The Avatar.
[Sniffs] Not impressed.
I'm trying to find
the spirit portals?
I opened one...
I heard Unalaq did that.
No, I did, but...
well, if you opened it,
how come
you don't know
where it is, huh?
[Sighs]
B-b-because I was
at the South pole.
- I don't trust her.
- Get out of our world.
- We don't need you.
- You don't belong here.
Get away from me.
[Groans]
Did you guys see that?
She tried to bend at us
in our own holes.
Get her!
[Screaming]
[Sighs]
Jinora!
[Groans]
Korra!
Stay calm.
Your energy is upsetting them.
You're only making it worse.
[Groans]
[Screams]
[Both scream]
[Tense orchestration]
[gasps]
[Screams]
[Gasps]
[Coughs]
[Sighs nervously]
Jinora!
[Gasps and coughs]
[Screams]
[Sighs]
Jinora?
Jinora.
[Pants]
Ah.
[Creature growls]
Jinora.
[Sobs] Jinora.
[Sobs]
Korra!
Where are you?
Hello?
I'm lost.
Can anyone help me?
[Creature coos]
Furry-foot, is that you?
[Laughs]
It's so good to see you again.
You're so big here.
I don't suppose you know
where Korra is, do you?
We were supposed to go find
the spirit portals,
but I don't know how to find
anything down here.
[Creature coos]
It's like
an awesome tree house.
Wait, I read about this place.
Grandpa Aang came here.
It's Wan Shi Tong's
spirit library.
[Hawk screeches]
Ah!
Get away!
[Hawk squeaks]
I'm sorry I swatted you.
You just scared me.
You two look lost.
Maybe I can help you.
I know you.
I was good friends
with Avatar Aang.
Iroh.
Hello, Korra.
I'm glad you came to visit us
in the spirit world, Korra.
You came just in time.
We're having a little tea party
to celebrate
May-Jim's wedding.
How can you marry each other?
Aren't you...
Complete opposites?
I know.
I tried to fight it,
but she really grew on me.
The spirit world is
very mysterious,
but so is love.
Help yourself
to some tea and cakes.
They are spirit cakes,
so you won't gain any weight.
Of course,
you won't lose any, either.
This part of the spirit world
isn't so scary.
My teapot.
That's right.
It was yours long, long ago.
When you were Avatar Wan,
you used it to carry
the light spirit Raava around
until the two
of you became one.
It's my favorite thing
I've found here.
You know,
when you make tea in it,
you can still taste
a little light in every cup.
[Creature squeaks]
[Dramatic music]
Wow.
I could just stay in here
forever, reading.
The last human who said that
is still here.
Professor Zei.
I see that you have
some knowledge of the past,
so you should know that humans
are no longer allowed
in my library.
Get out.
I thought anyone could come in
if they brought you
some new knowledge.
Those are the old rules.
Besides, what is a little girl
going to teach Wan Shi Tong,
he who knows 10,000 things?
Well, since you've been down
in the spirit world,
the humans have invented radio.
Yes, I am well aware
of the radio.
But do you know how it works?
Of course I do.
There is a box,
and inside the box,
there is a tiny man who sings
and plays musical instruments.
Actually, when we speak,
our voices produce sound waves.
Radio takes those sound waves
and converts them
into electromagnetic energy
that is transmitted
through the spectrum...
all right, enough.
I did not know this.
Apparently, I have been fed
some misinformation
about the existence of tiny men
in boxes.
[Dog squeaks]
Still, I'm not interested
in that human garbage.
Now go away.
My grandfather was the Avatar,
and I came to the spirit world
with the new Avatar
to find the spirit portals.
I would think
that you'd wanna help me.
You came with the Avatar, hm?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Fine, you may look around,
but don't break anything.
I'll know.
Come on, furry-foot.
We gotta hurry.
They say that the game
of Pai Sho
was invented by the spirits,
although some of them
don't seem
to grasp it very well.
Just hold on.
I'm thinking.
As you can see, it is a game
that requires great patience,
but time does not mean much
to us here.
How long have you lived here?
Oh, I've been here
for many years.
I had always enjoyed
the company
of the spirits, so when my work
was done in the material world,
I chose to leave my body behind
and come to the spirit world.
It can be a wonderful place,
and I've made so many friends.
Korra, what's wrong?
I came here with my friend,
but I lost her,
and now I'm all alone.
You're not alone, Korra.
It's okay.
No.
It's not okay.
Jinora's gone,
and I need to find her.
She's lost,
and we need to go home.
I don't like the spirit world.
I don't want
to be here anymore.
[Screams]
[Growls]
[Howls]
Did you say something to her?
Me? You're the one
with the big mouth.
Korra, please, stop.
Look at what you're doing
to everyone.
I did that?
In the spirit world,
your emotions become
your reality,
especially for the Avatar
because you are the bridge
between the two worlds.
You must try to stay positive.
[Sniffles]
I'm sorry.
There.
You see?
I can make the sun shine?
Even in the material world,
you will find that if you look
for the light,
you can often find it.
But if you look for the dark,
that is all you will ever see.
I'm looking for my friend.
I want her here now.
Why didn't she come out
like the sun?
I'm afraid finding her
won't be so easy.
But what am I supposed to do?
Sometimes, the best way
to solve
your own problems
is to help someone else.
This little fellow needs
to go home as well.
Maybe if you help him
find his friends,
you will be able to find yours.
I'll take him home.
Where do I go?
The dragon-bird nest
is located there,
at the top
of Hai-Riyo peak.
[Sighs]
It's not in here either.
I have to find the portals.
Korra's probably waiting for me
there right now.
I need to find a map
that shows
where the spirit portals are.
Could you help me?
[Dog groans]
[Dog whimpers]
[Dog panting]
Thanks.
This is it.
The tree of time.
That's where Avatar Wan
imprisoned Vaatu.
"The elders believed
that as long as the portals
"are closed during
the harmonic convergence,
"Vaatu will remain imprisoned
"and the battle
between good and evil
"will not be fought again.
"But if both portals
are opened,
"spirit energy
is amplified greatly.
"During the harmonic
convergence,
"this energy will be
great enough
"to allow Vaatu
to break free from his bonds,
"and the material world
will again risk
being consumed by darkness."
[Gasps]
We have to warn Korra.
Leaving so soon?
When Wan Shi Tong told me
he had a visitor,
I had to see it
with my own eyes.
I can't believe Tenzin
sent his daughter here
instead of coming himself.
What kind of a father is he?
Better than you.
Wan Shi Tong,
how can you be helping him?
Unalaq has proven to be
a true friend
to the spirits,
unlike the Avatar.
Why would you wanna help
Vaatu escape?
He'll destroy everything.
Don't believe everything
you read.
Why don't you come with me
so you can do
some first-hand research?
[Gasps]
[Creature growls]
Furry-foot?
This looks scary.
Will you come with me?
This is something
that you must do on your own.
The people who have been coming
to the spirit world lately
have brought darkness
and anger,
so that is what you see now.
But you have light and peace
inside of you.
If you let it out,
you can change the world
around you.
Besides, look
at this little fellow.
This Mountain is his home.
When you first met him,
you were frightened.
But does he seem scary
to you now?
No.
Many things
that seem threatening
in the dark become welcoming
when we shine a light on them.
It was good to meet you.
Come visit me again,
in this life or the next.
Bye.
Okay.
Time for you to go home.
[Lightning crashes]
Light and peace.
[Creature growls]
[Growling]
I'm not afraid of you.
You're not scary.
You just look that way.
I have light inside.
It's okay.
You can be my friends.
My name is Korra, and I'm taking
this dragon-bird home.
[Majestic orchestration]
[Panting]
[Giggles]
Iroh said you could be nice.
Do you wanna help me?
[Panting and growling]
[Birds chirping]
[Bird screeches]
All right,
now let's close that portal
and go find Jinora.
[Dragon screams]
[Tense music]
That's where Vaatu is.
[Dragon screeches]
So you've returned, Raava.
The harmonic convergence
is coming soon,
and this time, I'm going
to wipe you out for good.
I think you've said that
before, Vaatu,
but I'm here to close
the portal.
You're not getting out.
You might want to reconsider,
that is, if you want
to save your friend.
[Pants nervously]
Jinora.
[Hissing]
[Growling]
I can't believe I trusted you.
You made me think you wanted
to restore balance
with the spirits.
But this, this isn't balance.
It's madness.
Now let her go.
If you want your friend
to make it
out of the spirit world,
you'll open
the other portal now.
Don't do it, Korra.
[Sighs nervously]
[Gasps]
What will it be?
Open the portal,
or lose your friend's
soul forever?
[Gasps]
Stop.
I'll do it.
[Tense music]
[Creature screams]
Now, let Jinora go.
Ah!
You should have come
through the portal.
Then you could do this.
[Groaning]
[Sighs] [Screams]
Korra!
[Sighs]
[Groans]
[Shouts]
[Sighs]
[Sighs and groans]
[Dragon screams]
[Groans]
[Dragon squawks]
[Growling]
[Dragon screams]
I'll see you soon, Raava.
Once the harmonic
convergence comes,
I'll be free from this prison.
And then I will have
my revenge.
[Gasps]
[Pants]
Korra.
What was it like?
Did you manage
to close the portal?
Was Jinora able to help you?
Tenzin, I'm...
I'm sorry.
Where's Jinora?
W-why isn't
she waking up?
Korra.
What happened
to my little girl?