Earth. Fire.
Air. Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
The Avatar has gone missing!
Three years ago, Zaheer poisoned Korra,
severely injuring her.
While her friends moved
on with their lives,
Korra remained in the south pole.
Everyone thought she
was still recuperating,
but six months ago, Korra left
home and hasn't been seen since.
Even chief Tonraq was shocked to learn
that his daughter's
whereabouts are unknown.
What has become of the Avatar
and when will she return?
Hurry up in there!
Come on, I got an emergency situation!
Knock yourself out.
Huh?
You again.
Leave me alone!
What's wrong with her?
Young lady, are you all right?
Can I take you to a Doctor?
No, I don't need any help.
Now don't take this the wrong way,
but I can't wait for you to leave.
How else is she supposed to
take that but the wrong way?
I mean because I've never
had a pen pal before.
I'm going to write you so many letters,
and just to get the ball rolling,
here. Spoiler alert.
Pabu and I already miss you.
Thanks, that's sweet. Are
you sure you don't want
some company in the Southern water tribe?
- I'm happy to come with
you. - No, I appreciate it,
but I'll only be gone a couple weeks.
A little time alone will be good for me.
Now I don't want you to worry
about a thing while you're gone.
Your recovery should be
your number one concern.
Jinora, the airbenders and I
have everything under control.
Bye, Korra! Get better soon!
Don't forget to write!
Ah!
Can't sleep again?
Honey, your father and
I have tried to give you
as much space as you've
needed, but we're worried.
You're not sleeping. You're barely eating.
We don't want to push you,
but it's been three weeks.
Will you please go see Katara?
All right. I'll go.
You're going to get through this.
Oh, I love you so much.
The poison did a lot of internal damage.
Can you fix it?
I can help guide your healing process,
but whether you get
better or not is up to you.
I know what it's like to go
through a traumatic experience,
and I promise you,
if you dedicate yourself to getting better,
you'll recover stronger than ever.
That's what I want, more than anything.
Then try something for me.
Concentrate on your big toe.
Visualize it moving.
Breathe.
Did you see that?
It worked!
The mind can be a powerful ally
or your greatest enemy.
Now, I want you to try taking a step.
Ah!
Ugh!
You're okay.
Your body thinks it's still in danger,
but you're safe here.
Use your mind to overcome the pain.
Try again. I'm done for today.
"Dear Korra, I miss you.
"It's not the same in
Republic city without you.
"How are you feeling?
Things are going well here.
"I just got a big contract
"to help redesign the
city's infrastructure,
so I'll be keeping pretty busy for awhile."
"Hey, Korra.
"So, I'm not very good at writing letters.
"It's 2:15 in the
afternoon. Weather is fair.
"Chance of snow showers later today.
"But enough joking around.
I hope you're doing well.
"Me? I'm back on the beat.
"Beifong has me staking
out the red monsoon hideout,
you won't believe what's going down."
"My dearest, Avatar Korra.
"Though several fortnights have
passed since your departure,
"to convalesce in the
homeland of your tribesmen,
"I feel our friendship knows
neither time nor distance.
"You will be most pleased to learn
"that I found gainful employment
"with Sir Varrick and the lady Kuvira.
"I set off on the morrow
with some trepidation,
"but I am eager to offer any aid I can
in stabilizing the Earth kingdom."
Whenever you're ready. What's the point?
We've been at this for almost six months
and I can barely take a couple
of steps without collapsing.
I know you're frustrated, but...
Of course I'm frustrated!
A crazy man poisoned me,
and now I can't dress
myself or cook for myself
or do anything for
myself, and this whole time
my friends have been off helping the world
while I'm stuck with you,
and you can't even heal me!
That came out wrong.
It's all right.
Let your anger and
frustration flow like water.
I am trying to understand
why this happened to me.
But nothing makes any sense.
I'm tired, Katara. I'm so tired.
Korra, I know you feel alone right now,
but you're not the first Avatar
who's had to overcome great suffering.
Can you imagine how much
pain Aang felt when he learned
that his entire culture was taken from him?
That must have been so awful.
But he never let it destroy his spirit.
He chose to find meaning in his suffering,
and eventually found peace.
And what am I gonna find
if I get through this?
I don't know, but won't it
be interesting to find out?
Close your eyes.
Visualize yourself walking over to Naga.
Can you see it? Yes.
Now, take that first step.
Where'd you come from, little cutie?
You can see her, too?
If you can see her, too,
maybe I'm not going crazy.
How'd you do that?
You want me to follow you?
All right, let's see what I find.
It's so good to see you.
How have you been, Korra. You look great.
I feel great. Come on.
I want to show you how
much better I'm doing.
Attack! I can take it.
Ah! Ah!
All right, the sparring match is over.
I thought I was ready.
There is no shame in
taking the time you need
to make a full recovery.
Being the Avatar can wait.
But what about the Earth kingdom?
I hear it's still a mess out there.
The situation has been stabilizing
since Kuvira took charge.
But that should be me out
there fixing things, not her.
I know you want to help, but trust me,
everyone has this under control.
I just think you need to...
If you say, "be patient,"
I swear I'm gonna
watersmack you in the mouth.
No, I was going to say you need to...
Not worry about the future.
Be grateful for where you are now
and the progress you've made.
"Dear Asami, I'm sorry I
haven't written to you sooner,
"but every time I've tried,
I never knew what to say.
"The past two years have
been the hardest of my life.
"Even though I can get around fine now,
"I still can't go into the Avatar state.
"I keep having visions of Zaheer
and what happened that day.
"Katara thinks a lot of this is in my head,
"so I've been meditating a lot,
"but sometimes I worry
I'll never fully recover.
"Please don't tell Mako and Bolin.
"I wrote to you and not them.
"I don't want to hurt their feelings,
"but it's easier to tell
you about this stuff.
I don't think they'd understand."
Everything all right, sweetie?
There's something I need to tell you both.
What is it?
I want to go back to Republic city.
Are you sure? I know I'm not 100% yet,
but I feel like I've hit a wall.
I need to be where the action is,
where my friends are.
I'll have the white lotus prepare a boat
and they can take you back to Republic city
as soon as you're ready.
No, I want to go alone.
And have some time to clear my head.
It will be good for me.
Two lobster crabs, please.
Why, you're the Avatar, ain't ya?
Yep, that's me.
I can't believe it!
Mind if I take a picture
for my wall of avatars?
I'm kind of in a hurry.
It'll only take a second.
Avatar Aang was a big fan of
my seaweed wraps, you know,
so I named them "Aang rolls."
Now they're my biggest seller.
And they ain't even got fish in 'em.
Now smile.
But if could have met any Avatar,
I'd have to pick Kyoshi.
Taking down a shark squid with one hand?
Now that's a lady I'd like to get to know.
Thieves! Get back here!
Oh, don't worry. The Avatar's right here.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go get 'em!
Hand over the bags or else.
Ah! Ugh!
You sure she's the Avatar?
Everyone, come here! It's the Avatar!
You sure?
I don't sense any Raava energy around her.
Besides, she's not dressed like the Avatar.
Doesn't the Avatar have ponytails?
Do you mind? I'm trying
to concentrate here.
And, yes, I am the Avatar.
I'm just wearing different clothes
and I cut my hair.
See? I told you guys it was her.
How come you've been away so long?
I was hurt pretty bad awhile ago,
and lost touch with my Avatar spirit.
No wonder I couldn't feel Raava's energy.
I came to the tree of time
hoping to reconnect with Raava
and turn on the Avatar state again.
But it's not working.
The last time I was here
I saw all sorts of visions.
Now I don't see anything.
Maybe we can help you get better.
I'm sorry, but for years
people have been saying
they can help me get better.
Nothing's worked.
I need to figure this out on my own.
"Dear mom and dad,
"I arrived in Republic
city a couple weeks ago
"and couldn't be happier.
"It's nice to be back at the temple,
"and it's great to see my friends again.
"Don't worry, I'm taking it easy,
"but hopefully I'll be back in action soon.
"I miss you both very much.
"Please give Naga a big hug for me.
Love, Korra."
Raava?
Raava!
I am ending this.
Excuse me, who do I talk to
about getting in the ring?
Is that all you got?
We have a winner!
Hurry up in there!
Why did you bring me to the swamp?
Wait, I met you at the tree of time.
You should have told me who you were.
If I did, would you have followed me?
I get your point.
But why did you bring me here?
What am I gonna find in the swamp?
Not a what. A who.
No, wait!
Come back!
You're just in my mind.
You're not real.
Ah! Ugh!
Ahh!
Ah!
Help!
Feeling better?
Where am I? What happened?
I was hoping you could tell me.
I found you passed out in the mud.
How did you know I was out there?
I'm pretty tapped into
the goings-on around here.
What brings you to the swamp, anyway?
A spirit led me here
and told me I was supposed to find someone.
- Is that you?
- Beats me.
But if your Avatar senses called you here,
you should probably listen to them.
- Wait, you recognize me?
- In a manner of speaking.
We were good friends in your previous life.
I can't believe it.
Toph?
Nice to see you again, twinkletoes.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com