Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
1x08 - Field Trip
Report.
All sensors
are in the green, sir.
The building is secure.
I've heard that before,
mr. O'Brien.
Understood, sir.
Oh, and sir,
Your daughter
is here to see you.
Wonderful.
The old man
wants us on full alert, 24/7.
Report everything.
[whirring]
I'm in.
still no alerts showing up
on their systems.
You invented invisible armor,
Tony.
Think about that.
Your dad would be
so jealous.
he'd just come up with
something better.
This place used to be
my home.
Now I have to break into it.
[clanking footsteps]
When I was little,
I always wanted
To come down here
to my dad's vault
To see all of his inventions.
[static crackles]
It was the good stuff,
The stuff he couldn't
get to work
Or just never finished.
But now I'm scared
to look inside.
hey, you don't know
that Stane took it, Tony.
The living laser equipment,
It could have
gotten out there before.
no.
Stane took it.
Oh, man.
Stane's got everything.
then we'll get it back,
Because you've got something
he doesn't:
The iron man armor, right?
yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
I've got--huh?
[scattered beeping]
warning.
System failure
in progress.
All functions in shutdown mode.
[faltering beeping]
[tense music]
Tony?
Tony!
yeah, I'm here.
Tony, what happened?
the armor, it went, you know,
dead.
it went dead?
What did Stane do?
no, it wasn't Stane.
The power cells
are totally empty.
The stealth tech
must have fried them.
Whoops.
what are we gonna do?
There's no way you could carry
that armor out of the building,
And when Stane finds it--
relax, mr. Panicky.
This is no problem.
I'll just sneak
out of the building,
Grab some new power cells,
Sneak back in,
and get the armor.
Hmm, now that I said that
out loud,
I think maybe we are in trouble.
[slinky music]
okay, without the armor
to jam the cameras,
I'll have to do this fast.
When it's clear,
I'll jump into the elevator.
oh, you mean the elevator
that will set off an alarm
Without your armor to jam it.
[sighs]
So when it's clear,
I'll head up the stairs.
oh, what's happening?
don't worry.
I know this building like
the back of my hand.
There's no way I'm gonna get...
Caught.
whitney,
I do not have time for this.
you never have time!
I am dealing
with a major security breach,
And now you want to see me?
You?
Tony?
Tony!
Hi!
whitney?
I haven't see you
in, like, months.
Where have you been?
I heard
you're going to school now.
Why haven't you called?
[laughs nervously]
Sorry, whitney.
It's been a little crazy.
well, I'm sure you'll
find a way to make it up to me.
Maybe when you're done here,
we can--
whitney,
get out right now.
no!
You're busy, daddy?
Fine.
I'll wait.
don't let me keep you two.
what are you doing here
In the middle of the night,
Stark?
I can have the police here
in two minutes.
well, I--it's--
it's just that--
Look, I know it was wrong
to sneak in,
But you wouldn't let me
come anymore.
I couldn't help it.
This place,
I grew up here.
It's all I have left
of my dad,
And--and...
am I supposed to believe
you're crying?
you monster!
How can you be so cruel?
You kicked him out of the place
he grew up,
And now you're gonna arrest him
for missing his father?
this has nothing to do
with you, whitney.
ne.
I'm leaving.
And Tony's coming with me.
Or are you gonna
arrest us both?
mr. O'Brien,
Get them both
out of here.
I want every single floor
of this building searched.
Stark was here
for a reason,
And I want to know
what it is.
thank you, whitney.
my pleasure.
Now tell me why
you were really there.
wow, it's late.
I really have to go.
Rhodey's mom
is gonna be so mad.
Seriously, whitney,
thanks.
you'd better call me.
wow, when you screw up,
you do it big.
you can quit
cheering him up now, Pepper.
did you even lock the vault
behind you?
oh, no.
sorry, but can't you just
hop in another suit
And go get the one
you left behind?
whiplash trashed the only
other one that worked.
The rest aren't ready,
And we don't have time
to get them ready.
okay, what if we hope
really, really hard
That no one
ever goes down there?
that vault is the only thing
on that level,
And if it's been cleared out,
There's really no reason
someone would go down there.
Maybe Stane
won't suspect anything.
there's no way, dude.
There's no way Stane bought
that sob story you gave him.
He knows you were
up to something.
He's probably searching
the building right now.
And even if he's not,
It's not like he's going to
hand us visitor's passes
To get back in
any time soon.
that's it.
Iron man is finished.
wait.
Rhodey's right.
Stane won't hand out
visitor's passes to us,
But Stark international
might give out the passes
To the tomorrow academy.
uh, and that helps us how?
two words:
Field trip.
here's how it's gonna work.
The goal is to get
to the armor, get it working,
And get out
of Stark international
Without anyone seeing us.
Step one:
Get whatever tools, gizmos,
or batteries we need
To ma the armor work again.
what are you doing?
what?
This is the most important meal
of the day.
then Tony calls
whoever he still knows
At Stark international,
Someone who
owes him a favor.
tricia?
It's me, Tony, Tony Stark.
Tony?
I heard you came in here
last night.
Are you okay?
someone that can authorize
a tour of Stark international
For the tomorrow academy.
please?
Dad used to do this thing
all the time,
Tours, charities,
demonstrations.
Can you help?
My dad always said
I could count on you.
I--I'll see
what I can do, Tony.
I'll take care of getting
the trip
Authorized by the school.
Principal nara is all about
students showing initiative.
Pepper,
I like your initiative.
but what he really loves
is paperwork.
I'm afraid you'd have to get
permission slips
For eh and every student,
signed by their--oh.
as hall monitor,
I've busted about every kid
in the academy
For hallway violations.
I got their parents' signatures
from the reports.
a school tour?
Is this a joke?
no, mr. Stane.
We do it to keep up
the company's image
And to maintain ties
with the community.
the company's image
is no concern of--
oh, and your daughter's
on line four.
Rhodey can handle
transportation
And professor klein.
He shouldn't take
much convincing.
I'm just having
such a hard time
With the concept of fusion.
really?
You got an "a" on the test.
that was just luck.
Uh, I totally guessed.
But it just so happens
that Stark international
Is having a demonstration
of their fusion reactors today.
So can we have class there?
I'd love to see
their labs.
Uh, can we do that?
there's a bus
waiting outside, sir.
I can't believe that worked.
how couldn't it work?
Now, once we get inside,
We'll cause a distraction
and split off from the tour,
Then get to the armor.
Piece of cake.
Pepper, if you ever go evil,
We're all in trouble.
[snorts]
tell me about it.
[excited chatter]
Stark.
hey, uh, gene.
What's up?
good question.
What exactly are you up to?
And don't lie,
because you're really bad at it.
I have absolutely no idea
what you're talking about, none.
see what I mean?
You're a terrible liar.
You, potts, and rhodes
had to go to a lot of trouble
To make this
little excursion happen.
we love science, man.
Nothing weird about that.
Now let's go in, please.
come with me.
gene, don't forget to give
Rhodey his lunch.
He gets really hungry.
that fell apart fast.
What now?
I don't know.
Plan "a" was so awesome,
I didn't come up
with a plan "b."
I'm guessing
that there's something
Much more interesting in here
than Rhodey's lunch.
You should have
asked me to help.
Both: [sigh]
okay.
One of us will have
to get to the armor
Replace the power cells,
and fly it out.
ooh-ooh-ooh.
I call it.
and stay out.
[laughs]
You got kicked out.
thanks, happy.
Why aren't you inside?
dude, I was kicked out
before I even got off the bus.
go to school, whitney.
see, I value time
with my father more than school.
Too bad you don't feel
the same way about your work.
[phone rings]
what is it, O'Brien?
sir, Tony Stark just tried
to enter the building.
We ejected him,
But he's on
a school bus outside.
he's planning something.
Have you completed
the sweep of the building?
sir, there are 110 floors
in the building
With thousands of rooms.
We've completed 87%.
enough.
Finish the sweep,
And put Stark
under surveillance immediately.
and this
is our fusion reactor lab,
Where our scientists
work on ways to create
New, clean, and inexpensive
power sources
For the good of the world.
or weapons.
[hisses]
Will you focus?
Look, I have to be the one
to get the armor.
I know it inside and out.
And I know how
to change the power cells,
You don't.
okay, fine.
Crybaby.
I'll do the diversion.
[sneaky music]
[glass shatters]
[alarms blare]
uh, fire?
that isn't a fire alarm.
It's a hazardous
material station.
oh, good to know.
no, I'm not trying
to rob the place.
I left something in there,
And I really want
to get it back.
Just help me find a way
to get in.
um, is it worth you doing
my science homework
For the next month?
uh, sure.
What are you--
Smack!
aw, dude, sorry.
Loose ball.
You okay?
and stay there.
what happened to her?
hazmat station.
Just keep her here until
O'Brien comes down.
oh, come on.
I thought I saw
some toxic waste, for real.
You might want to go back
and check.
get me a visual
on Tony Stark.
He should be on the bus
outside.
Is that him?
I want this building
in lockdown, right now.
boo.
[screams]
Uh, I'm pretty sure I'm gonna
beat you up when we get home.
fair enough.
Opening the door now.
[electronic beeping]
I seriously can't believe
we did it--
[shrill alarms wail]
you did it, all right.
[nervous chatter]
and that concludes
today's tour.
what did you do?
nothing.
The door was already unlocked.
I was just opening it.
Uh-oh.
uh, what's going on?
Is it a meltdown?
Is the building going nuclear?
Oh, tell me the truth!
Oh, it's a meltdown!
what?
No, it's not a meltdown.
get me out of here!
[electronic chime]
[groans] take that.
and just how are we
supposed to get out, genius?
[buzzing drone]
no problem.
See?
They're cutting a way out
for us.
there's no way
we're not going to be seen.
And the stealth tech
will just fry the armor again.
Stane will know that
we're involved with iron man.
I'll probably get arrested,
If these security drones
don't fry me first.
[laughs nervously]
status?
security drones have
activated on all levels
Per lockdown protocol.
If Tony Stark
is in the building,
They'll find him.
Hmm, that's weird.
See, on sublevel "Z,"
The drones are trying
to get into a room
That was cleared out weeks ago.
Stark's vault.
Get me a visual
on the vault, now!
O'Brien!
someone cut power
to the building.
But you can only do that
from right...
I am through being ignored!
great.
Clang!
I surrender.
[explosions]
what did I miss?
[laser blasts]
we have to get out
before the power comes back on.
[loud explosion]
Wait.
What are you--
[rapid laser fire]
I can walk.
Let me down!
we're taking a shortcut.
Zap!
well?
it, uh,
it takes a minute
For the grid to reboot, sir.
[engines whirring]
let me down.
trust me,
you don't want that.
[short booster blast]
[laser fire]
[explosion]
[adventurous music]
stop!
Let me off here.
I'll rejoin the group.
It'll be less suspicious.
but it'll be dark in there.
You sure you don't want me
to stay to hold hands?
just go.
Crash!
we're up and running again.
But the security camera
hard drives, they--
Uh-oh.
find Stark.
Find him now.
piece of cake.
I don't even want
to hear about it.
what is your problem?
[laughs]
I got foam in my nose--
in my nose!
Did you get to wear
the armor?
Ha, no.
Don't tell me.
one side, move!
yo, cue ball.
Can't you see we're busy?
Stark's been helping me
with my homework all morning.
you were inside
the building.
There are hundreds
of security cameras.
I'll find a--
uh, sir?
The hard drives crashed
when the power went out.
All of today's
surveillance video, it's gone.
I'm thinking
two months of homework.
yeah, sounds fair.
well, that went perfectly.
Except for every single detail.
Well, it was a good plan,
though.
yeah, I'm sure
you meant for gene, happy,
And Stane's own daughter
to help us.
Man, it's just pure luck
That Stane doesn't have
the armor right--
Tony, where is the armor?
oh, that?
Yeah, uh...
I may need some help
getting it back.
[triumphant music]
sync:  f1nc0
thx to Adriano_CSI
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org