2x26 - The Makluan Invasion,
part 2 - Unite!
All right, guys, this is it.
The Makluans aren't messing around.
This is full-scale invasion.
No problem: Three of us
versus 60,000 aliens.
It's a good thing I can go
to the bathroom in my armor.
Tony, before the Earth gets annihilated,
and we're all reduced to
flaming microscopic cinders,
I just want to say one thing.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on, Pepper.
Listen. We're not going to die.
No matter what, we're
going to win this fight!
Sure. Tony, just let me say one thing
I've been wanting to say
for a very, very long time.
Look out!
There's too many!
Computer, contact Nick Fury.
General Fury, if you can
hear me, we need your help!
Eat molten plasma, alien scum.
Yah!
Hah!
I've always wanted to say that.
Nice job, Rescue,
but keep your eyes on
your radar, 3:00 doom!
[maniacal laughter]
Overlord, these fools are nothing.
This whole planet is insignificant.
Take me as prisoner, and
let the Earth live on.
Noble but foolish, Gene Khan.
Do you think mere
intentions make you a hero?
You're nothing without
the 10 rings of power.
As for your vile planet, extermination.
Rescue, 4:00!
7:00! 2:00!
I've got ships coming in at,
like, all o'clock, okay?
Like, every hour of the...
[screaming]
- Pepper!
[groaning]
War Machine, Rhodey, no!
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~
♪ He's a man on a mission ♪
♪ in armor of high tech ammunition ♪
♪ trapped on the edge
of an endless game ♪
♪ his teenage life
will never be the same ♪
♪ in a dangerous world
he does all he can ♪
♪ he's Iron Man ♪
♪ Iron Man. ♪
Nick Fury? Black Widow?
We've been trying to clear the streets.
We thought they'd abducted you.
It's a long story.
I'm okay.
I think I only broke my brain.
Come on, Rescue, we've got to move!
All right, you ugly alien freaks.
Show me what you've got!
Aagh!
Guess they've got a
lot more than I thought.
[groaning]
Hawkeye?
You know, I made a bet I'd never live
to see the apocalypse,
and here I am.
Great, lost a bet and get
to see the end of the world.
- Clint. I was sure you were...
- Dead, Tasha?
Nah, I'm still up and kicking.
How about a lift?
How about dinner and a movie?
I hear there's a great
alien invasion flick playing.
Does he ever shut up?
We need to gather our forces
and hit the mothership.
Where is Iron Man?
Help those people down below.
I'll try and handle the ships.
Um, right.
No problemo.
Everyone keep moving.
Get to safety.
There's an evac station
on 49th and Broadway.
Dad? Oh, no!
Iron Man?
Oh, how do I activate the
voice modulator thingy?
Not Iron Man, Mr. Potts.
- You can call me... Rescue.
- Wait, how do you know my name?
Ah, you're a famous federal agent!
And I'm a big fan.
But Da...  um, I mean,
Mr. Potts, be safe.
Huh.
Why can't aliens ever be friendly?
It's just like sci-fi movies.
They either want to wipe
us out or blow us up!
And when you are friendly,
it's always a trick to eat us.
[screaming]
War Machine, Rescue, General Fury,
the skies are clear, for now.
It's not attacking, not making a move.
This is the calm before the storm.
They're testing us.
The Makluan Overlord has
10 extremely hi-tech rings
that allow him control over reality.
If he wanted to, he could wipe us out
faster than we could blink.
No, it's all a game to him.
Yeah, he proved that when he
made us fight in his arena.
So, what do we do? We can't
attack him straight on.
The big refrigerator's right.
How do we take down
an alien ship the size of Manhattan?
Dad, come in.
How's the device coming along?
Working as fast as I can, son.
The last cannon was more precise.
It took weeks to build it.
This one is a bit on the shoddy side.
If it doesn't nullify the rings...
At this point I'd take a slingshot
if I knew I stood a chance.
I'll give you the heads
up when it's finished.
These champions continue to intrigue me,
particularly the one called Iron Man.
He's a selfish individual,
unlike you, human.
Iron Man and his friends
are nothing if not stubborn.
- They won't give up.
- Let us see how he fares
against one of the robotic
protectors of the planet Mongo.
We call him Ultimo.
Okay. What is that?
A robot we fought a long time ago,
when it was a guardian of a ring.
Can you bring it down with Extremis?
I've been trying since
these lizards showed up.
It's useless. Their tech is too alien.
We need strategy.
Iron Man, you and your team hit high.
- We'll hit low and trip up his feet.
- With what, a giant banana peel?
With these.
One thermal disc can take out a tank.
Everyone, move!
We'll distract it.
We will?
[groaning]
Look out!
Oh, man, oh, man, aah!
Gotcha!
When I switched teams to the good guys,
nobody said we would be fighting aliens.
I thought, you know, bank
robbers and dudes in tights.
You always said you wanted
to go out in a blaze of glory.
- How about an explosion of glory?
- Everyone keep quiet and focus!
We have to wait till that
walking skyscraper isn't looking.
Fury, Widow, no!
Iron Man!
[Hulk roaring]
The Hulk?
Hey, tin man. I told you I'd
be back when you needed me.
Time for Hulk to smash!
Haha, the Hulk!
All right!
If there's one thing I love
to break, it's giant robots!
Woo!
Thanks, big guy.
Incoming call from Roberta Rhodes.
Mom?
Uh, I'll take it.
James, where are you?
I'm worried sick.
I've been trying to call your cell.
I'm good, Mom. Are you okay?
I'm fine, baby. I need
you to stay in New Jersey.
I'm going to meet you at
uncle Nick's as soon as I can.
Uh, yeah.
Uncle Nick's. Sure.
Mom, gotta go. I love you!
Now, while the sensors are scrambled,
General Fury, it's up to your team.
Hawkeye, take out the left foot.
Black Widow, we'll take the right.
Tasha, if we get out of this, you
want to run away to Paris with me?
I'm almost on the verge of
saying "let's go right now"!
Let's hope this is
enough to bring it down.
Only three explosive arrows left.
Uh-oh. Robo-jerk's
going to get up again!
Iron Man!
What are you doing?
Okay, that was stupid, but
it looked awesome, right?
You see that, huh, you
big-eyed grey-skinned,
red-necked abducting
extra-terrestrial losers?
Let's not upset the angry E.T.'s any more
than we already have,
okay, Hawkeye? Thanks.
Oh, no. Everyone move!
This is the Black Panther.
It seems the smaller nation
comes to the aid of the bigger.
And I couldn't be happier for it.
Everyone, toward Panther's Quinjet.
Time to regroup and strategize.
The heroes flee. A pity.
And now, I will make my announcement,
as all honorable Makluan Overlords must.
Announcement?
What are you talking about?
The announcement proclaiming
the end of the world.
The Earth has given up.
The entertainment is over.
It is time to wipe this
planet out of existence.
I've tried contacting other
vigilantes and superheroes.
No one's responding.
My intuition tells me
that their games are over.
These beings are readying for a
massacre. You can smell it in the air.
So, what's the plan?
We don't have time for jibber-jabber.
I've got one. It's probably going to
get us all disintegrated,
but either way it's armageddon.
So, here it is.
First, we form two teams.
Team A will enter the ship here,
through this top port. I theorize
this will lead directly
into the reactor core,
which we'll have to blow
to detonate the ship.
Great! As long as I'm not
a part of team A, I'm cool.
Team B will have to break
into the hangar, smash through
and take out the Makluan
Overlord in his throne room.
Both missions are critical to success.
He-he. On second thought,
I'll sign up for team A.
So, who are the teams?
The strongest and most armored
members: Iron Man, War Machine,
Rescue and Hulk will
deal with the Overlord.
The rest of us will take
out the reactor core.
Iron Man! Uh...
Tony, wait.
I just, uh, want to talk to you before...
we head off to certain doom.
Pep... uh, Rescue,
now isn't the best time, seriously.
I, I have to contact my Dad.
Dad, come in.
Are you there?
I'm here, son. The Makluan
energy disruptor is finally a go.
Theoretically, it's 80 times
more powerful than the old canon.
Uh, just haven't tested it yet.
So, you don't know if it works?
That's comforting.
Huh, right... I have to align
it to the Stark 1 satellite.
It will help pinpoint the
beam to a remote target.
Great. The only problem
is, how do you get it there?
Hmm. I need a rocket ship and...
a space suit.
Uh-oh. I'm getting a wide
frequency transmission
from the Makluan mothership.
This doesn't look good.
I'll project it with my
holographic projector beam.
Simians of Earth,
I am the supreme Overlord
of the Makluan race.
You have proved
yourselves inferior beings.
Your military is weak,
Your heroes
nothing but lowly cowards.
I am here to rid the universe
of the thoughtless, primitive,
self-centered race of...
This is it.
We have to move now!
I'm down. Let's do this!
Heroes unite!
Let's go beat up some bad guys.
But do not fear, humans.
The residual energy from
your exploding planet
will be recycled to fuel our ship.
Long live the Makluan empire!
Never!
[laughing]
Your heroism is only blind eloquence.
Now I shall liquefy the
flesh from your bones!
[screaming]
What? Intruders?
The human warriors are back!
[roaring]
Let's show these aliens
how we do things on Earth.
Get 'em!
It's all or nothing.
We have to get to the Overlord.
Yeah, but we don't even
know how to find him.
Whoa! Hulk, take out those
robo-dragon... uh, whats-its!
With pleasure!
Eat this!
[screaming]
If there's one thing I hate more
than aliens, it's alien machines.
- Finally!
- Dad, come in.
How's everything going
inside the space armor?
Great, son, handles like a charm.
I'm almost at the satellite.
Attaching now.
It's going to take about 20 minutes.
20 minutes?!
Ah!
- Thanks, Rescue!
- Now we're even. Hah!
The soldiers are down. Now what?
We've got to find the throne room.
I hope this works!
If there's one thing Iron
Man knows, it's technology.
The reactor core.
I, too, have explosives to donate.
Um, guys, we're not exactly alone here.
Keep moving! We have to break
this line to get to the reactor.
[groaning]
[screaming]
Consider the line broken.
Hah, these guys aren't so tough. Ah!
Rick!
Okay.
Just a bit dizzy for you, babe.
Can you cut the jokes
and take this seriously?
You love it.
Ah!
Come, Nick Fury.
Let us plant some seeds.
I like the way you think, Panther.
They are here.
So, I guess he keeps you as
his pet rat now, huh, Gene?
I'm doing everything I
can to help, okay, Stark?
- I never wanted this.
- Well, this is where your greed got us.
You're no protector of the planet.
You're its destroyer!
Aptly said, Iron Man.
Come, let us battle. I seek a challenge.
That makes two of us,
lizard breath. Uh!
Whoa! The Makluan Overlord's
just as strong as the Hulk?
Yeah, 'cause of the rings.
You're done, baby!
Never!
Hah! The great grey beast was
another monkey. How appropriate.
And now, here stands our
three armor-wearing animals.
I'll say one thing, Overlord.
I'd rather be a monkey
than an extinct dinosaur!
He's too strong!
Time to bust out the bunker buster!
My turn.
- Are you setting the timer?
- Just about to... uh!
The timer still needs to get set.
Hawkeye, can you...
already on it.
Come on. Let's move!
There's more of them coming.
I sense an entire army!
Back to the Quinjet, now!
Hah!
Hah, stupid alligator!
You're finished, Overlord!
We're going to... uh...
we're here to put an end to you!
Oh, great.
Might as well give up now.
We're taking you down.
[laughing]
Dad, what's going on with
that Makluan disruptor?
I'm having serious trouble, son.
I can't calibrate the
targeting system to the ship.
Just activate the beam, Dad.
I've got a plan.
I'm going to control the
targeting system with Extremis.
I may not be able to
control Makluan tech,
but that doesn't mean I don't
have a few tricks up my sleeve.
[groaning]
What is this?
It's called Extremis.
I'm shutting you down, lizard!
No! The rings!
Useless!
This can't be!
No!
We did it! He's down!
The rings are temporarily disabled!
Iron Man, come in.
You have 60 seconds to get out
before the whole place blows!
- We have to go!
- Wait! Where's Gene?
[laughing]
Oh, no.
The Mandarin has returned!
The rings belong to me!
Get out!
The place is going to blow.
I'll take care of the Overlord.
- Gene, get them out!
- Tony, no!
Must shut down the power core!
Forget it. It's over!
Warning.
Reactor core at critical mass.
Detonation in 5 seconds.
Uh-oh.
Tony? Oh, no!
No!
Everyone can relax.
The alien menace has ended.
Tony, Stark!
Way to go, Tony!
- Oh, man!
- Well, the more, the merrier.
[people cheering]
- Huh?
- Ooh.
I can't believe it!
All this, time?
James Rhodes, you are
grounded until you're 22.
Right after I give you the
biggest hug you've ever had!
I have to say, Patricia,
I always knew my
daughter was a superhero.
Oh, I love you, too!
And it's Pepper, Dad.
Or even better, Rescue!
[chuckling]
Tony. You saved the day, and
everyone knows you're Iron Man.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, long story.
- You did it, Dad. You're a hero.
- I think that would be you, son.
He's right. Without your plan,
we wouldn't have stood a chance.
You're a natural leader, son.
Can I just say one thing to you?
You could, but there's something
I'd like to say to you first.
Huh, another diversion, hey?
Oh, Tony.
Okay, you guys are embarrassing
me. I'm feeling queasy here.
Can I just ask one thing?
What happened to Gene?
Something tells me
we won't be hearing from him.
You were right, mother.
Perhaps I'm not supposed
to rule the world.
Perhaps I'm supposed to protect it.
So, the entire world knows we're
superheroes. What do we do now?
Well, at least we don't have to lie
to the parental units anymore...
but yeah, this is going to be
a big change in our lives.
For the better.
For once, things feel good...
hopeful.
Like everything's right in the world.
Let's just make sure
it stays that way.
series sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~